filelisting.com 2019-08-07

# Privacy Policy - FileListing

### Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting FileListing.com ("the Website" or "this Website") FileListing.com owners ("we" or "us") values its visitor’s privacy. It is important to us that you understand what information we collect when you visit the Website either from a computer or a mobile device and what we may do with that information, so we have laid it all out here for you.

By using this Website you consent to the terms of this [Privacy Policy](), and you signify your assent to all of the terms of this [Privacy Policy]() and our Terms of Use. If you do not agree with any terms of this [Privacy Policy]() or our Terms of Use, please do not use this Website or submit any personal information. Please take care to read this terms to be sure you are informed about how your information may be used. Please also read our Terms of Use. 

Please note that this [Privacy Policy]() does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that we do not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by us. If you visit a site or resource that we mention or link to, (this includes any third party advertising companyes) be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information. 

**What we do with your personally identifiable information**

It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. "Personally identifiable information" means information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as, for example:

  * Your name, company, email address, phone number, billing address, and shipping address.

  * Your account user ID and password you provided when you registered to this Website.

  * Credit card information (this provision may not be appropriate if credit card information is handled by a payment processor).

  * Any account-preference information you provide us.

  * Your computer’s domain name and IP address, indicating where your computer is located on the Internet session data for your login session, so that our computer can ‘talk’ to yours while you are logged in.

If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, either directly or through a reseller or other business partner, we will:

  * Not sell or rent it to a third party without your permission, we may use your contact information to provide you with information we believe you need to know or may find useful, such as (for example) news about our services and products and modifications to the Terms of Use.

  * Take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

  * Not use or disclose the information except:

    * As necessary to provide services or products you have ordered, such as (for example) by providing it to a carrier to deliver products you have ordered.

    * In other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented.

    * In the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined (for example, statistical compilations).

    * As required by law, for example, in response to a subpoena or search warrant.

    * To outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential.

    * As necessary to enforce the Terms of Use.

    * As necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of us, its users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.

**Other information we collect**

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of the Website; research and development; customer and account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely. 

**Cookies**

We uses "cookies" to store personal data on your computer. We may also link information stored on your computer in cookies with personal data about specific individuals stored on our servers. If you set up your Web browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Firefox) so that cookies are not allowed, you might not be able to use some or all of the features of this Website. 

**External data storage sites**

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

**Your privacy responsibilities**

To help protect your privacy, be sure:

  * Not to share your user ID or password with anyone else.

  * To log off the Website when you are finished.

  * To take customary precautions to guard against "malware" (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. If you have provided us with an email address, we may notify you, by email to that address, of any material change to how we will use personally identifiable information. 

**Questions or comments?**

If you have questions or comments about this [Privacy Policy](), send an email to [admin@filelisting.com](mailto:admin@filelisting.com).

FileListing.com is a powerful search engine that lets you locate files currently available on the internet.  
Our bots are continuously scanning, indexing and cataloguing files other people are downloading.
